Guide to the Richard Pollay. Tobacco industry promotion (TIPS) collection, 1885-2012 and undated RL.11612
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 800. Audiovisual Materials, 1964-2010; undated; 1
  - A13. Houston Herstek Favat, Dept. of Public Health Radio Historical Reel (PSAs), undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-014)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The Beginning/The Twenties, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-015)
    American Advertising Museum (set of 6 cassettes + 13 pp. printed booklet)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The Thirties Part I, II, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-016)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The Thirties Part III/The Early Forties, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-017)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The War Years Part I, II, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-018)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The Late Forties Part I, II, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-019)
  - A14. Audio History of Commercial Radio. The Early Fifties/The Late Fifties, undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-020)
  - 8002. 1930s-1940s radio cigarette commercials, undated (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-021)
  - 8002. 1930s-1940s radio cigarette commercials--backup copy, undated (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-022)
  - 9002. Smoke Free, 1988 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-023)
  - The Best of Marlboro Country Music vol. 1, 1985 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-024)
  - Winston Lights Holiday Music Collection vol. 2, 1991 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-025)
  - Marlboro Man theme, undated (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-026)
  - Marlboro Man theme, undated (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11612-CAS-027)
  - 138a. The Insider, 1999 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-001)
  - 261. History of Advertising: Animation 1930-1940, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-002)
  - 262. History of Advertising: Animation 1940-1950, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-003)
  - 263. History of Advertising: Animation 1950-1960, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-004)
  - 264. History of Advertising: Automobiles 1930-1940, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-005)
  - 265. History of Advertising: Automobiles 1940-1950, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-006)
  - 266. History of Advertising: Automobiles 1950-1960, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-007)
  - 267. History of Advertising: General 1930-1950, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-008)
  - 268. History of Advertising: General 1950-1970, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-009)
  - 8051. NASCAR Winston Cup Series, 2001 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-010)
  - 8051. NHRA drag racing, Pomona Calif., 2001 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-011)
  - The Ad and the Ego official study guide, undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-012)
  - Things Go Better with Coke: Sixties Coca-Cola Commercials 1965-1969 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-013)
  - Censored by a Cigarette: Musical Empowerment Against Tobacco. Dan Eumurian and Friends, 2002 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11612-OP-014)
  - 20th Century Cigarette Advertising Notes, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11612-OP-015)
  - 5002. Science, Tobacco and You/La science, le tabac et vous!, 1999 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11612-OP-016)
  - 5007. Bullshit and Ruses: Richard Pollay, Harm Reduction Summit, 2004 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11612-OP-017)
  - 6008.1. Expert panel--Final, undated (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11612-OP-018)
  - 6008.1. Influence of Tobacco Power Wall Advertising on Children, 2005 (Box AV12, Video-disc RL11612-OP-019)
  - 6015. Surgeon General Report: Women and Smoking, 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL11612-OP-020)
  - 6036. International Expert Panel on Cigarette Descriptors, 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL11612-OP-021)
  - 6036. Physicians for a Smoke-Free Canada: Tobacco industry documents, spotlight on compensation, 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL11612-OP-022)
  - 6026. Physicians for a Smoke-Free Canada: World No Tobacco Day Forum on Tobacco Industry Documents, 2000 (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-023)
  - 8054. Health Canada Guildford documents, undated (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-024)
  - 8054. JTI-MacDonald v. Attorney General of Canada: Pollay exhibits, trial transcripts and reports, 2002 (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-025)
  - 8054. PSC Guildford documents with hyperlinks, undated (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-026)
  - 8054. PSC Guildford documents: Anne Lavack's summaries with hyperlinks to 228 Guildford documents, undated (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-027)
  - 8054. Physicians for a Smoke-Free Canada: Selected trial documents, 2002 (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-028)
  - 8054. Physicians for a Smoke-Free Canada: Tobacco documents, 2000 (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-029)
  - 8054. Tobacco industry documents #8 assembled by PSC, undated (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-030)
  - 8054. Washington State trial exhibits disk 1 of 1, 1999 (Box AV14, Video-disc RL11612-OP-031)
  - Kick in the Asphalt Band: Official Winston Cup "No Bull" Series CD, 1997 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-032)
  - 2013 addition. "Bullshit" presentation, UCSF, 2004 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-033)
  - 2013 addition. Chesterfield box 1; 59 television spots. LG0155483, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-034)
  - 2013 addition. Chesterfield box 2-3; 85 television spots. LG0155484; TRT 87:00, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-035)
  - 2013 addition. Chesterfield box 4-5; 85 television spots. LG0155485; TRT 1:03:00, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-036)
  - 2013 addition. Cigarette reel 1; TRT 61:00, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-037)
  - 2013 addition. Cigarette reel 2; TRT 61:00, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-038)
  - 2013 addition. Cigarette TV Ads 1950s & 1960s; A Pack of Lies, Vancouver Institute lecture, 1997 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-039)
  - 2013 addition. Classic Radio Commercials: 396 commercials 1920s-1970s. Earthstation1.com; list included, 2004 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-040)
  - 2013 addition. Common knowledge files and exhibits for R. Pollay from Louis Kyriakoudes, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-041)
  - 2013 addition. Corporate Deceit: Big tobacco's target, 2001 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-042)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 1 (0f 23): Canadian brands, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-043)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 2 (0f 23): Minor brands, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-044)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 3 (0f 23): Benson & Hedges, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-045)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 4 (0f 23): Camel 1, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-046)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 5 (0f 23): Camel 2, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-047)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 6 (0f 23): Chesterfield, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-048)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 8 (0f 23): Kool, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-049)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 9 (0f 23): L&M, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-050)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 10 (0f 23): Lark, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-051)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 11 (0f 23): Lucky Strike, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-052)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 12 (0f 23): Marlboro, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-053)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 12 (0f 23): Marlboro, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-054)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 13 (0f 23): Newport, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-055)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 14 (0f 23): Old Gold, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-056)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 15 (0f 23): Pall Mall, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-057)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 16 (0f 23): Parliament, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-058)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 17 (0f 23): Philip Morris, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-059)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 18 (0f 23): Salem, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-060)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 19 (0f 23): Tareyton, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-061)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 20 (0f 23): True, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-062)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 21 (0f 23): Virginia Slims, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-063)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 22 (0f 23): Winston, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-064)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Cigarette TV Ads; DVD 23 (0f 23): Viceroy, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-065)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives: 801-12 Emergence of Advertising in America--Tobacco Advertising vol. 1, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-066)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives: 801-12 Emergence of Advertising in America--Tobacco Advertising vol. 2, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-067)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Selected TV Cigarette Ads of the 1950s, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-068)
  - 2013 addition. History of Advertising Archives Selected TV Cigarette Ads of the 1960s, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-069)
  - 2013 addition. Kool Mixx, 2004 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-070)
  - 2013 addition. 801-10. Life Magazine collection vol. 1: index of tobacco advertisements; 1953-1969 advertisements, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-071)
  - 2013 addition. 801-11. Life Magazine collection vol. 2: 1970-2002 advertisements; covers, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-072)
  - 2013 addition. Marketing to Youth: Evidence from corporate documents (presentations), 2001 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-073)
  - 2013 addition. Pack of Lies. Media Education Foundation, 1994 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-074)
  - 2013 addition. Pollay presentations: Bullshit; Disclosures; Understanding Ads (Powerpoint format), undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-075)
  - 2013 addition. Pollay publications: Advertising history and social/cultural effects (not tobacco), undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-076)
  - 2013 addition. Pollay publications: Influential works on tobacco, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-077)
  - 2013 addition. TV Cigarette Commercials: The Classics; Earthstation1.com, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-078)
  - 2013 addition. TV Cigarette Commercials: The Classics; Earthstation1.com, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-079)
  - 2013 addition. U.S. Cigarette Radio Ads 1933-1952, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-080)
  - 2013 addition. U.S. Cigarette Radio Ads 1933-1952, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-081)
  - 2013 addition. U.S. Tobacco Print Advertising (20th C.); Dr. Jackler (Stanford) collection; 100s of Powerpoint files, 2010 (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-082)
  - 2013 addition. Vintage Cigarette Commercials, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-083)
  - 2013 addition. Young Adult Target; Pam Ling, Ontario TC conference keynote, undated (Box AV15, Video-disc RL11612-OP-084)
  - 2013 addition. 9004. Candy cigarettes database, undated (Box AV15)
  - 8054. Canadian Guildford document summaries 1998-2000 (ZIP drive), undated (Box AV14)
- 900. Slides, 1885-2002; undated; 2
  - Benson & Hedges, 1968-2002; undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Camel, 1915-2002; undated; 8 folders (Box 1)
  - Chesterfield, 1915-1975; undated; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Kool, 1939-1995; undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Lucky Strike, 1900-1997; undated; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Marlboro, 1920s-1995; 6 folders (Box 1)
  - Marlboro, undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Merit, 1977-1995; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Pall Mall, 1908-1990; undated (Box 2)
  - Salem, 1959-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Virginia Slims, 1969-1995; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Winston, 1955-1995; undated; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Minor brands--A, 1939-1992; undated (Box 2)
    Includes Adam, Admiral, All, Alligator, Alpine, Aspen, All American, American, American Spirit, Arctic Lights, Austin, Avalon
  - Minor brands--B, 1915-1995; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Includes Backwoods, Barclay, Basic, Beech Nut, Belair, Best Buy, Between the Acts, Black Cat, Bloomer Club, Boots, Brandon, Bravo, Bright, Brighton, Brookwood, Brotherhood, Bucks, Bull Durham, Bust the Trust
  - Minor brands--C, 1889-1994; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Includes Cambridge, Cameo, Capri, Carlton, Cartier, Cavallier, Century 100's, Chelsea, Clown, Coffin Nail, Colony, Cookie Jar, Coupon, Creole, Cronn's, Cross-Cut, Cycle
  - Minor brands--D, 1920-1995; undated (Box 2)
    Includes Dakota, Dave's, Dawn, Day and Night, De-Nicotea, Decade, Deities, Diplomat, Domino, Doral, Doublets, Dr. Scott, Drum, Duke, Duke's Cameo, Du Maurier, Dunhill, Durham Whiff
  - Minor brands--E, 1949-1992; undated (Box 2)
    Includes Eclipse, Embassy, Encore, Eve
  - Minor brands--F, 1910-1975; undated (Box 2)
    Includes Fact, Falcon, Fatima, Favorite, Fleetwood, Frappe
  - Minor brands--G, 1890s-1994 (Box 2)
    Includes Galaxy, Gold Plate, Golden Lights, GPC
  - Minor brands--H-J, 1894-1994; undated (Box 2)
    Includes Hale, Half and Half, Harley Davidson, Hassan, Helmar, Heritage, Hit Parade, Hogshead, Holiday, Home Run, Honest, Horizon, Iceberg, Jade, John Alden, Johnnie Walker, Julep
  - Minor brands--K, 1953-2000; undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Includes Kamel, Kent, Kentucky Kings, Kentucky Winners
  - Minor brands--L, 1932-1992; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Laredo, L&M, Lark, Life, Listerine, Long Johns, Lords
  - Minor brands--M, 1917-1994; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Magna, Mail Pouch, Malibu, Makaroff, Marshall's, Marvel's, Maryland, Masterpiece, Matinee, Maverick, Max, Mecca, Melachrino, Mercer, Misty, Mogul, Montclair, Moonlight, More, Multifilter, Murad
  - Minor brands--N, 1974-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Nebo, New Cig, New Leaf, Newport, Next, Northwind, Now
  - Minor brands--O, 1910-1999; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes O-Nic-O, Oasis, Old Chum, Old Gold, Old Judge, Old North State, Omar, Omni, Our Advertiser
  - Minor brands--P, 1915-1995; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Parliament, Paxton, Perfection, Pet, Philip Morris, Piedmont, Pimlico, Players, Polo, Premier, Prince Albert, Pyramid
  - Minor brands--Q-R, 1918-1991; undated (Box 3)
    Includes Quality, Raleigh, Ramses, Real, Refined, Regent, Rembrant, Reyno, Richland, Ritz, Riviera, Royal Farms
  - Minor brands--S, 1929-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Safeway, Sano, Saratoga, Satin, Savannah, Savvy, Seventy, Shahdur, Sherman, Signature, Silva Thins, Sove, Spearmint, Splendid, Spring, Spud, Sterling, Stride, Stud, Style, Sub Rosa, Sunshine
  - Minor brands--T, 1936-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Tall, Tall 'N Slim, Tareyton, Target, Tempo, Tennyson, Tourney, Trim, Triumph, True, True Gold, Turkey Red, Turkish Trophies, Tuxedo, Twenty Grand, Twist
  - Minor brands--U-V, 1885-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes Vanguard, Vantage, Viceroy, Virginia, Virginia Brights/Richmond Straight Cut, Virginia Leaf, Virginia Rounds, Viscount
  - Minor brands--W-Z, 1963-1966; undated (Box 3)
    Includes Waterford, Wave, Winchester, Wings, Worth, Yara, York, Zarina, Zephyr
  - Canadian advertising--Benson & Hedges, undated (Box 3)
  - Canadian advertising--Du Maurier, 1983-1985; undated (Box 3)
  - Canadian advertising--Players, undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Canadian advertising--Miscellaneous A-L, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes Belmont, Belvedere, Buckingham, Cameo, Canadian Classic, Craven A, Dunhill, Export A, Kool
  - Canadian advertising--Miscellaneous M-Z, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes Matinee, MacDonald, Medallion, NO. 7, Peter Jackson, Rothman's, Sweet Caporal, Vantage, Viscount
  - Canadian advertising--Titles and other slides, undated (Box 4)
    Includes slides of miscellaneous advertising, logos, clippings
  - Canadian and International advertising (Box 4)
  - Cartoons, 1977-1988; undated (Box 4)
    Includes political cartoons, tobacco-related characters in popular cartoons (Doonesbury)
  - Chewing and spit tobacco, 1920-1993; undated (Box 4)
    Includes advertising for tobacco-related products, chewing and spit tobacco (Skoal), Cigars; see Series 6031 for additional cigar slides
  - Healthy promotions presentation (WP96.16), 1996 (Box 4)
    Includes advertising with health-related messages: doctor recommendations, filter technology, tar content, "light" brands; slides depict advertising dating 1930-1992 (inventory in folder)
  - Magazine coverage of cigarettes presentation (WP97-11), 1997 (Box 4)
    Text in folder including hard copies of some slides
  - Miscellaneous binder 1, 1954-1990; undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes anti-smoking messages, smoking prevention and cessation, public service advertisements, Pro-smoking and smoker's rights messages, tobacco industry advocacy, tobacco industry corporate advertising
  - Miscellaneous binder 2, 1930-2000; undated (Box 4)
    Includes slides on smoking and women, youth smoking, smoker research, press coverage of tobacco, tobacco product packaging and trademarks, smoking-related graphs and tables
  - One Hundred Illustrations of 20th Century Cigarette Advertising (WP97.10), 1997 (Box 4)
    Slide presentation created for viewing at tobacco-related trials; inventory in folder
  - One Hundred Illustrations of 20th Century Cigarette Advertising (WP97.10)--Color master, 1997; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 1: Last used and culled slides, undated (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 2: Titles, cartoons, graphs, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 3: Public relations, industry, smoking prevention, undated (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 4: Pre-1953 U.S. advertising, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 5: Medical, filters, low tar, undated (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 6: Target marketing: youth, women, ethnic, undated (Box 4)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 6: Target marketing: youth, women, ethnic, undated (Box 5)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 7: Camel, Marlboro, menthol, undated (Box 5)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 8: New tactics and tools, undated (Box 5)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 9: Canada best and last used, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Pack of Lies presentation 10: Canada titles, etc., undated (Box 5)
  - Presentation: Bold and Beautiful or Black, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
    Slides from 1930s-1990s
  - Retail cigarette advertising, 1990s (Box 5)
    Includes store signs, point of sale displays, some outdoor advertising
  - Retail cigarette advertising--Street facing, 1997 (Box 5)
    Includes outdoor signage viewed in Texarkana and Portland, Ore. Brands include Marlboro and Camel. Includes billboards, retail signs. Text with hard copies of some slides in folder
  - Titles 1, undated (Box 5)
    Includes title slides for presentation decks, collection of tobacco-related advertisements
  - Titles 2, undated (Box 5)
  - Transnational Firms vs. State Monopolies: Lessons in Competitiveness from Marlboro Country (WP95.2), 1995 (Box 5)
    Includes a selection of global cigarette advertising slides dating 1930-1995; text of presentation in folder; sheet of Malaysian cigarette advertising; also includes text of The Empire Strikes Back: Responses of the Global Tobacco Industry to the Decline of Traditional Markets (WP95.3)
  - Trinkets and trash slide collection, 1996 (Box 5)
    Compiled by Trinkets and Trash Services; includes slides of a variety of tobacco industry promotions: catalogs, coupons, point of purchase displays, billboards, special packs, warning labels, matches, cigars; inventory in foldler
- 950. Print Advertising, 1906-2006; undated; 3
  - Small Format, 1906-2006; undated; 1
    - Basic, 1993-2001; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Belair, 1973-1990 (Box 6)
    - Benson & Hedges, 1960-1999; 5 folders (Box 6)
    - Camel, 1913-2000; 8 folders (Box 6)
    - Camel--Promotions, 1989-2001; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Carlton, 1964-1999; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Chesterfield, 1921-1993; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Doral, 1972-2000; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Kamel, 1996-1999 (Box 7)
    - Kent, 1953-1995; 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Kool, 1936-2006; 5 folders (Box 7)
    - L&M, 1958-1978 (Box 7)
    - Lark, 1969-1992 (Box 7)
    - Lucky Strike, 1916-2000; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Marlboro, 1928-1995; 5 folders (Box 7)
    - Marlboro, 1990-2000; 8 folders (Box 8)
    - Marlboro--Promotions, 1958-2001; 4 folders (Box 8)
    - Marlboro--Sports, 1971-2002; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Merit, 1976-2000; 7 folders (Box 8)
    - More, 1974-1989 (Box 8)
    - Newport, 1971-2001; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Now, 1975-1993; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Old Gold, 1927-1978 (Box 9)
    - Pall Mall, 1916-2001; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Parliament, 1952-2000; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Philip Morris, 1940-1990 (Box 9)
    - Players, 1983-1996 (Box 9)
    - Raleigh, 1930-1985 (Box 9)
    - Salem, 1957-1999; 6 folders (Box 9)
    - Tareyton, 1954-2000 (Box 9)
    - True, 1970-1990; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Vantage, 1971-1997; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Viceroy, 1948-1993; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Winston, 1955-2003; 10 folders (Box 10)
    - Women's brands--Capri, 1987-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Women's brands--Misty, 1991-1999 (Box 10)
    - Women's brands--Virginia Slims, 1970-2001; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Women's brands--Virginia Slims, 1997-2001 (Box 11)
    - Women's brands--Minor brands, 1971-1999; 2 folders (Box 11)
      Includes Dakota, Eve, Max, Newport Slim, Newport Stripes, Ritz, Satin, Style
    - Minor brands--A, 1946-2000 (Box 11)
      Includes Alligator, Alpine, American, American Spirit, Arctic Lights, Aspen
    - Minor brands--B, 1916-1992 (Box 11)
      Includes Backwoods, Barclay, Bright, Brookwood, Bucks, Bull Durham
    - Minor brands--C-E, 1917-1998 (Box 11)
      Includes Cambridge, Capri, Cartier, Cavalier, Cemetery, Century, Chelsea, Colony, Cross-Cut, Crown's of London, Dave's, Decade, Drum, Duke, Du Maurier, Dunhill, Egyptian Deities, Embassy, Eve
    - Minor brands--F-L, 1915-2001 (Box 11)
      Includes Fact, Fatima, Golden Lights, GPC, Half and Half, Helmar, Hit Parade, Holiday, Horizon, Iceberg, Jade, Juleps, Just Black, Kentucky Winners, King Sano, Laredo, Long Johns
    - Minor brands--M, 1906-1998 (Box 11)
      Includes, Magna, Malibu, Maryland, Masterpiece, Max, Mercer, Misty, Montclair, Moonlight, More, Multifilter, Murad
    - Minor brands--N-R, 1917-2003 (Box 11)
      Includes Natural American Spirit, Next, Now, Omar, Omni, Paxton, Piedmont, Pyramid, Real, Regent, Richland, Ritz, Riviera
    - Minor brands--S, 1929-1984 (Box 11)
      Includes Saratoga, Satin, Scotch Buy, Seventy, Sherman's, Silva Thins, Spring, Spud
    - Minor brands--S-Y, 1930-1998 (Box 11)